<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GameScreen</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="shareGame">Share Game</string>
    <string name="descriptions">Description</string>
    <string name="applyInternship">Play Game</string>
    <string name="lets_go">Let\'s Go</string>
    <string name="editphoto">Edit Photo</string>
    <string name="apply">Play</string>
    <string name="benefit">Requirements:</string>
    <string name="requirements">How to play:</string>
    <string name="good_morning">Good Morning</string>
    <string name="name">Patricia</string>
    <string name="find_game">Find Game To Play...</string>
    <string name="latestgames">Latest Games</string>
    <string name="profilename">Patricia</string>
    <string name="see_all">See All</string>
    <string name="popular">Popular This Month</string>
    <string name="allgames">All Games</string>
    <string name="on_boarding_1">Welcome to GameScreen!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string-array name="requirement_gojek">
        <item>sample text</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="howtoplay_tetris">
        <item>The aim in Tetris is simple; you bring down blocks from the top of the screen.
        You can move the blocks around, either left to right and/or you can rotate them.
        The blocks fall at a certain rate, but you can make them fall faster if you are sure of your positioning.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="howtoplay_2048">
        <item>Use your arrow keysSwipe with your fingers to move the tiles. Tiles with the same number merge into one when they touch. Add them up to reach 2048!</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="howtoplay_monopoly">
        <item>Starting with the Banker, each player throws the dice. The player with the highest total starts the play.
Then each player places his token on the corner marked "GO", and throw the dice and move his the number of spaces indicated by the dice.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="howtoplay_scrabble">
        <item>
A player begins the game by placing a word on the star square at the center of the board. This star acts as a double word score.
            The star cell does not act as a double word score for subsequent players playing off the center square. Play continues in a clockwise direction around the Scrabble board.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="howtoplay_drawmy">
        <item>One player is the artist - when their turn starts, they get 3 words to choose from, and then they have to draw the chosen word.
            The other players try to guess what the artist is drawing.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="howtoplay_glowhockey">
        <item>Enjoy this unique air hockey game with neon lights and a futuristic vibe! Hit the disc and make it slide into your enemies net. Protect your side and win!</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="howtoplay_tictactoe">
        <item>When you’re the first one up, there is a simple strategy on how to win tic tac toe: put your ‘X’ in any corner.
            This move will pretty much send you to the winner’s circle every time, so long as your opponent doesn’t put their first ‘O’ in the center box.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="howtoplay_checkers">
        <item>Play consists of advancing a piece diagonally forward to an adjoining vacant square.
            Black moves first. If an opponent"s piece is in such an adjoining vacant square, with a vacant space beyond, it must be captured and removed by jumping over it to the empty square.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="htp_tetris">
        <item>sample text</item>
        <item>sample text</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="requirement_microsoft">
        <item>sample text</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="benefit_microsoft">
        <item>sample text</item>
        <item>sample text</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>